

NORAMIRAH BINTI ARWIN

+6019 417 6621 noramirah.arwin@yahoo.com

D/A Arwin Bin Marasap, Jabatan Kerja Raya, Peti Surat 75, 89057 Kudat, Sabah

ABOUT ME

Name: Noramirah Binti Arwin

ID Number: 921001 12 5822

Nationality: Malaysia

CGPA: 3.11/4.00

SKILLS

MICROSOFT OFFICE

COMMUNICATION

ORGANISATION

INTERPERSONAL

DRIVING LICENSE

LANGUAGES

ARABIC

REFERENCES

1. Puan Tai Nyuk Chin

Lecturer, UiTM Sabah 012 892 1021

2. Tuan Haji Pg Putra Pg Omar

Group Agency Director (GAD)
Putra & Associates (Etiqa Takaful Berhad)
019 821 1515
pgputra@ymail.com

OBJECTIVES

I am Noramirah, graduated from Universiti Teknologi Mara (UiTM) pursuing in Bachelor in Business Administration (hons) Business Economics also Diploma in Banking. I would like to be part of a company where I can enhance my skills and gain work experience for the future development of myself.

WORK EXPERIENCES

Apr 2017-Nov 2017

Government Enhancement Programme (SL1M) Trainee in Administration Department Koperasi Pangeran Haji Omar (PHO)

Aug 2016-Feb 2017

Assistant Supervisor
Supervise and monitor staff
Watson's Personal Health&Care Sdn Bhd Ampang

Feb 2016-Jul 2016

Internship as admin Filling foam and registration of member Pertubuhan Peladang Kawasan Kudat

Nov 2015-Feb 2016

Clerk Issue invoice&Filing Benar Jaya Enterprise Sdn. Bhd.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION

(2014-2017)

UNIVERSITI TEKNOLOGI MARA (UITM)
BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION (HONS)

BUSINESS ECONOMICS

DIPLOMA **(2011-2014)**

UNIVERSITI TEKNOLOGI MARA (UITM)

DIPLOMA IN BANKING

(20045-2009) SEK. MEN. KEB. PINAWANTAI

PMR.SPM